

Ahmad Trad

Nationality: Syrian Date of birth: 28/11/2000 Gender: Male

Companies Companies Comp

Website: https://ahmad-trad.netlify.app/

• Home: Damascus, Damascus (Syria)

ABOUT ME

Hi, I'm Ahmed Trad, a web developer and graphic designer with a passion for creating beautiful, functional, and user-centered digital experiences. With 3 years of experience in the field. I am always looking for new and innovative ways to bring my clients' visions to life.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer

xten [01/10/2018 - 30/01/2019]

City: Damascus **Country:** Syria

• Tasked to make graphics for off line and offline layouts.

• Edited editorial photos for clients and magazines, and social media posts

Front-End Developer

codex [15/06/2019 - 30/11/2019]

City: Damascus **Country:** Syria

- · Working on developing the interfaces of various websites
- Maintaining and modifying destination software and creating others
- · Splitting pages into parts and organizing files
- give clean code

Front-End Developer

wizme [02/05/2021 - 30/08/2022]

City: Damascus **Country:** Syria

- Working on developing the interfaces of various websites
- Maintaining and modifying destination software and creating others
- Splitting pages into parts and organizing files
- give clean code

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

INFORMATION ENGINEERING

Al-Ittihad Private University [15/09/2018 – Current]

City: Damascus **Country:** Syria

WEB DEVELOPER

New Horizons Institute [03/01/2019 – 28/05/2019]

City: Damascus Country: Syria

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Arabic
Other language(s): English

DIGITAL SKILLS

Html / Css / JavaScript / React.js / Redux / React-Router / React-Query / Next.js / Tailwind / Material UI / Three.js / Scss